 
 every dollar counts, so count on Vulcan. 
 No matter what type of foodservice operation you have, greater efficiency leads to greater profits. It's especially true in your kitchen, where utilizing the most energy-efficient equipment is your most effective way to manage ever-increasing monthly power bills. That's why it makes sense to replace older equipment with ENERGY STAR®-qualified products. They'll not only save you hundreds of dollars every year on your utility bills, they might even qualify you for a credit from your state or energy provider.  