   Vulcan innovation:  better for the environment, better for the bottom line.  
 Being the industry's leader in innovation goes beyond achieving the ultimate in cooking performance, reliability and durability. It's ensuring that, throughout our product portfolio, we deliver the level of quality you've come to expect from Vulcan while helping you to maintain a profitable, sustainable operation that's efficient, productive and environmentally sound. 
 
 
    Being the industry's leader in innovation goes beyond achieving the ultimate in cooking performance, reliability and durability. It's ensuring that, throughout our product portfolio, we deliver the level of quality you've come to expect from Vulcan while helping you to maintain a profitable, sustainable operation that's efficient, productive and environmentally sound. 
  This is the fourth straight year ITW FEG has received this award after earning back-to-back Partner of the Year Awards in 2008 and 2009. 
 
 
       
 
 