 about vulcan 
 Masterful design. Precision performance. State-of-the-art innovation. For over 130 years, Vulcan has been recognized by chefs and operators throughout the world for top-quality, energy efficient commercial cooking equipment that consistently produces spectacular results. Trust Vulcan to help make your culinary creations turn out just right—each and every time. 
 Vulcan is associated with the Vulcan Food Equipment Group and is a division of the ITW Food Equipment Group. 