 company overview 
 
 Our history can be traced back to 1865 and a foundry company in Louisville, Kentucky that manufactured cooking stoves and other products. That operation would later become part of the Hart Manufacturing Company. 
 The Vulcan name first appeared in 1890 with the formation of the Vulcan Gas Heating Company. Through the early 20th century, both companies grew and continued to add product lines. 