 In 1949, Vulcan-Hart was formed when Hart Manufacturing Company acquired the Vulcan name and line of commercial products. The new company continued to expand its product lines, both through acquisitions and through research and development. 
 Today, Vulcan is among the world's largest manufacturers of commercial cooking equipment, with worldwide distribution of the broadest lines of gas and electric equipment.  
 Ready for us to bring the heat to your kitchen?  Contact us now . 
   