 International Product Notice 
 The Vulcan FEG products, services, capabilities, programs and promotions described on this site generally are available to customers doing business within the 50 states of the United States of America. Vulcan FEG is an international company committed to meeting the food equipment needs of customers and markets around the world. As such, our products, services capabilities, programs and promotions may vary by region or country. Specifically, some Vulcan FEG products, services, capabilities, programs and promotions described on this site may not be available in countries other than the United States of America, or in United States of America installations, possessions, or affiliated territories outside the 50 states of the United States of America. For information on Vulcan FEG products, services capabilities, programs and promotions available outside the United States, please contact your nearest Vulcan FEG representative. 
 For support outside the United States, please contact us. 
 Limitations of Use by Visitors from Outside the United States 
 This Web Site is presented by Vulcan FEG from within the United States. Vulcan FEG makes no representation that materials in the Web Site are appropriate or available for use in locations outside the United States. Neither the Web Site, nor any underlying information or technology may be downloaded or otherwise exported or re-exported into, or to a national or resident of, any country to which the United Sates has embargoed goods (for example, Cuba, Iran, Iraq, Libya, North Korea, Sudan, Syria) or to anyone on the U. S. Treasury Department’s list of Specially Designated Nations or the U. S. Commerce Department’s Table of Denial Orders. By downloading or using any element of the Web Site, you are agreeing to the foregoing and you are certifying that you are not located in, under the control of, or a national or resident of any such country or any such list. In addition, you are responsible for complying with any and all local laws in your jurisdiction which may impact your right to use the Web Site. 