  French Quarter Flair, Fired by Vulcan 
  Dickie Brennan's has been named one of America's 10 best steakhouses by Maxim Magazine, designated a "Power Table" location by The Wall Street Journal, and received the Wine Spectator Award of Excellence. 
 It's a restaurant that has hit its stride and then some. Yet, amazingly, New Orleans' Dickie Brennan's Steakhouse found itself literally submerged in the aftermath of Hurricane Katrina. But with a healthy dose of determination, and help from Vulcan, it's back stronger than ever. 
 "After the storm, we had an opportunity to go with whatever equipment we wanted," said Managing Partner Steve Pettus. "But it seemed like a strong family connection between our group and Vulcan. When you find a great product like this, it's a lot easier to go forward with it." 
 Vulcan made New Orleans restaurants a priority after the storm and provided Dickie Brennan's Steakhouse with the  heavy-duty ranges  Pettus calls "incredibly versatile" and "very well built." 
 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/About_Vulcan/Testimonials/dickies.jpg 
 