  Vulcan Broiler, Michael Lomonaco Approved 
  Renowned chef Michael Lomonaco's newest contribution to the Big Apple's considerable line of fine restaurants takes the traditional steakhouse to a new level. And Vulcan is proud to have supplied the broiler that he considers integral to his menu. 
 Porter House New York, located in the Time Warner Center, features an emphasis on succulent meats in tandem with premium seafood and the finest in American ingredients and flavors. 
 "The steakhouse is the ultimate American restaurant," says Lomonaco, "it's hospitality without formality." He chose the  Vulcan broiler  to cook his signature meats after an exhaustive search. "We were looking for a broiler that could perform in the modern, contemporary steakhouse, one that would deliver the crunchy-char finish that people associate with a great steak. It's a workhorse, and it has the durability and reliability we require." 
 Lomonaco visited the Vulcan test kitchen and put the unit through its paces before making this important decision. "At the end of our due diligence, and once having met the people, from the sales reps and design engineers to the manufacturing reps, it convinced me that Vulcan was a company I could partner with—that meant a lot to me," he added. 
 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/About_Vulcan/Testimonials/porter_house.jpg 
 