  Retirement Community Puts Vulcan Equipment Through Its Paces 
  As the baby-boom generation moves toward retirement, a new marketplace is born. And Vulcan supports the growth of these retirement communities with dependable, and productive equipment for all their foodservice needs. 
 St. Andrews Estates North is a retirement life community in Boca Raton, Florida. The Mediterranean-style campus sits on 65 lushly-landscaped acres and is home to 420 seniors that enjoy top-quality food prepared in a kitchen stocked with Vulcan equipment. 
 The head chef and staff oversee the preparation of 750 meals a day—giving their four  Vulcan convection ovens  quite a workout. These diverse ovens do a lot—from baking, roasting and braising to being used as back-up steamers. The even heating and low maintenance is important because they are in operation nearly 15 hours a day. They are vital to St. Andrews' diverse menu featuring nine entrées each day. Favorites include roasted chicken, fish, veal and lamb shanks, and lasagna. 
 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/About_Vulcan/Testimonials/Providing_Care.jpg 
 