  Chef's Table Menu Perfect Match for Vulcan Endurance Range 
  In its seven years of existence, Chef's Table restaurant in Orem, Utah has won numerous awards including an "Excellent" rating from Zagat and being named "Best in Utah" by the Chamber of Commerce. 
 This success has fueled the restaurant's growth and its need to equip the kitchen with ranges that meet the demand. "Almost every item on the menu is served or finished à la minute," said Executive Chef Kent Anderson. "The range in this restaurant is the backbone of what we do." 
 Two years ago Anderson added a  Vulcan Endurance™ Range  to his line-up, and its performance was such that when his second range "was on the verge of dying," his choice for a replacement was easy. "We added a second Endurance," he said. 
 "Everything about this range is smarter—you can tell that when they designed it. Vulcan took the time to talk to people that actually cook on these ranges. There's more work space on the front, the oversized heads, superior firing capacity, they even have the knobs hidden on the front so they don't get hot and burned-up. It's a better built range." 
 As Chef's Table prepares its newest seasonal menu, Anderson can proceed with confidence knowing the Vulcan Endurance Ranges that are the "backbone" of the kitchen will be up to the task: "It's one of the best pieces of equipment I've ever bought, and you know I mean it, because I bought it again." 
 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/About_Vulcan/Testimonials/chef_table.jpg 
 