  Vulcan Steam Equipment Helps Fleming's Keep Customers Coming Back 
  Fleming's Steakhouse &amp; Wine Bar is not your father's steakhouse. That's by design. "We serve 100 wines by the glass, which is very unique. We have soft woods, brighter lighting and music in the foreground. This appeals to women, who generally don't care for the traditional dark, cigar-smoky steakhouse," said Baltimore franchise Chef/Partner Eric Littlejohn. 
 But Fleming's is about a lot more than ambiance. Customers come in droves for the prime cuts of aged beef, fresh seafood and array of succulent sides. And they turn to Vulcan for the steam to keep it moving. "The  Vulcan steamers  are just wonderful. We use them for all of our vegetables and many seafoods," says Little john. "They are in constant use and when we have a need, we call Vulcan and they are right here ready to take care of us." 
 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/About_Vulcan/Testimonials/flemings.jpg 
 