  You know it's solid and you know it's going to work right 
 "You know it's solid and
you know it's going to work right," said Patrick Morrow, executive chef of
Ryleigh's Oyster seafood restaurant and raw bar in Baltimore and Hunt Valley,
Maryland. Chef Morrow has seen the difference the  PowerFry™  makes in his
kitchen. "It's given us better product in general. You have a more consistent,
crispier product with a more even fry," he reports. Along with increased production
and energy efficiency, Patrick appreciates the direct interaction he's had with
the fryer's engineer. 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/About_Vulcan/Testimonials/reigh.png 
 