  Vulcan's fryer was the only one that could handle the volumes I expect 
 "Vulcan's fryer was the only one that could handle the volumes I expect," says Dewey Guida, owner/operator of DeeJay's BBQ, a high-volume restaurant and lounge in West Virginia.What impresses Dewey most about the  PowerFry™  is its quick heat recovery and ability to produce the crispy fries, zucchini and breaded fish he needs to please his customers. When it comes to Vulcan, he says, "They are amazing with their support and concern. They stand behind the product." 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/About_Vulcan/Testimonials/dejay.png 
 