 what is infrared cooking? 
 Infrared waves are a form of energy that’s similar to light. We use these infrared waves to transfer heat to food more quickly and efficiently than traditional convection, conduction or steam heat transfer methods allow. Infrared cooking reduces the air circulation and eliminates conduction heat transfer by separating the heat source from directly touching the food, resulting in a better food product. 