  infrared cooking  
 Infrared is the primary energy form of all non-microwave technology. Ceramic infrared burners produce up to 35% of its energy in the infrared spectrum, with the remaining 65% is transferred through hot air convection. These burners heat the ceramic to temperatures over 1000°F, causing it to glow red and emit infrared energy. 
 The common feature to all infrared emitters is that they glow—you can see the light they give off. For the purposes of cooking, this glow is wasted energy. The most efficient infrared cooking appliances generate emissions without also generating light.  
 That's where IRX™ Technology comes in. 