 A typical gas charbroiler uses a combination of convection
and conduction cooking. As the burner heats, hot air rises and circulates
(convection), which can pull moisture out of the food. The charbroiler grates
also transfer heat by directly touching the food (conduction). 
 Vulcans VTEC charbroiler is engineered to create an
infrared cooking profile using a patented burner design which converts the high
temperatures of the burner box into infrared radiation through the emitter
panel. A stainless steel cooking grate complements the system optimizing
the infrared cooking profile.  