   
 Fully MIG welded frame 
 Stainless steel front, sides, backriser, lift-off high shelf 
 6" stainless steel adjustable legs 
 30,000 BTU/hr open top burners with lift-off heads for easy cleaning 
 Shrouded flashtube pilot system (1 pilot per every 2 open burners) saves $300 per year in energy costs 
 Cool-to-the-touch control knobs 
 Heavy duty cast grates, easy lift-off 12" x 12" in front and 12" x 14" in back 
 Extra deep grates in back accommodate large pans or stock pots 
 Extra deep stainless steel pull-out crumb tray with welded corners to contain liquids 
 35,000 BTU/hr bakers depth standard oven allows 18" x 26" sheet pans to fit side to side or front to back in 36", 48", and 72" ranges (sheet pans fit front to back in 24" and 60" ranges) 
 Superior baking performance 
 Oven thermostat adjusts from 250-500º F with low setting  
 Oven controls mounted in insulated side compartment on all models (except 24" range) to keep controls out of the heat zone 
 2 racks and 4 rack positions 
 1-year limited parts and labor warranty 
 
 
 The Endurance Range is built with Vulcan's legendary toughness, precision and dependability and loaded with innovative features sure to make an impact on your kitchen. 
 79725652 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/48-Range-(2-Burners,-36-Griddle).png 
  
  
 465 
 9 
 