   
 Infrared burner design delivers fast heat-up times 
 Stainless steel front, sides and top—looks good and cleans easily 
 Aluminized steel interior and exterior bottom panel 
 Chrome-plated wire shelf—standard with 3 rack positions 
 17½" deep x 21¼" high 
 VICM design uses efficient infrared burners to deliver penetrating heat and simple operation 
 
 
   VICM
Series Cheesemelters are designed with stainless steel sides, front and back to
ensure durability and facilitate cleaning. They provide penetrating heat
quickly for maximum efficiency in any kitchen environment.   
   
    
 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Cheesemelter_ICM36_Right.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Cheesemelter_VCM48_Right.png 
  
 785 
  
 