   
 Stainless steel front, sides and top 
 Dual temperature controls 
 6-position adjustable grid 
 Grid measures 27 1/2 in. x 13 in. 
 Removable full-width spillage pan 
 Standard voltage 240 V 
 
 
    
  An adaptable energy efficient back-up broiler or a convenient food warmer. 
    
   
 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/36ESB_Elec_Salamander.png 
  
  
 482 
  
 