   
 Stainless steel front, sides, back riser, high shelf and 6" adjustable legs 
 28,000 BTU/hr two piece cast iron top burners 
 12" x 12" cast top grates 
 3" wide stainless steel front top ledge creates a convenient landing area 
 Standard oven adjusts from 250º F to 500º F 
 35,000 BTU standard oven (V24 is 28,000 BTUs) 
 
 
 For greater cost efficiencies, consider Vulcan's V Series Economy Range line. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/v-series.png 
  
  
 483 
 