   
 2 high-powered 55,000 BTU/hr ring-type burners in each section—110,000 BTU/hr input per section 
 Stainless steel front and sides with chrome plated legs standard 
 Standing pilot ignition with 2 infinite control manual gas valves for each section 
 Heat shield protects gas valves from high temperature, extending valve component life 
 Heavy duty cast iron top grates support large stockpots 
 22 1/2" - 24" high working height 
 
 
   Vulcan Stock Pot Ranges
include heat shields designed to extend valve component life by protecting gas
valves from high temperature. With heavy duty top grates made of cast iron, they
can support even the largest stock pots.  
    
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VSP100-1600x1700.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VSP200F-1800x1700.png 
  
 484 
 