   
 Stainless steel front, front top ledge, burner box, sides, base and stub back 
 1 1/4" front gas manifold 
 1 1/4" rear gas connection (capped) 
 4" stainless steel stub riser 
 Heavy duty cast grates and aeration bowls 
 6" stainless steel legs 
 4" flanged feet for all modular top units 
 Stainless steel cabinet base doors and adjustable universal slides with stainless steel shelf for cabinet base models (no shelf or slides in 12" wide cabinet bases) 
 Porcelain over steel oven cavity 
 Griddles available left or right 
 
 
 The performance to tackle today's demands. The flexibility to meet tomorrow's. The V Series is our latest line of intelligently designed heavy duty ranges that features the ultimate in durability, innovative features and true versatility. V Series ranges are modular from top to bottom and side to side, giving you maximum freedom for your kitchen and your menu. Best of all, the unique design of the V Series allows for complete customization as your needs change. 
 47668356 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/prod_HD_V2B36S_L.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/prod_HD_V2B36S.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/prod_HD_V2B36S_R.png 
 570 
  
 