   
 Stainless steel front, front top ledge, burner box, sides, base, exterior bottom and stub back 
 1 1/4" diameter front gas manifold with 1 1/4" rear gas connection (capped) 
 17,500 BTU/hr. burner 
 Individual pilots and controls for each burner 
 1/2" polished steel plate 
 3 sided grease trough 
 4" stainless steel stub riser 
 6" adjustable stainless steel legs for "B" models (no legs for modular model) 
 Stainless steel cabinet base door 
 Universal rack guides, with one removable shelf (cabinet base) 
 One year limited parts and labor warranty 
 
 
 The performance to tackle today's demands. The flexibility to meet tomorrow's. The V Series is our latest line of intelligently designed heavy duty ranges that features the ultimate in durability, innovative features and true versatility. V Series ranges are modular from top to bottom and side to side, giving you maximum freedom for your kitchen and your menu. Best of all, the unique design of the V Series allows for complete customization as your needs change. 
 47668356 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/prod_HD_PLANCHA.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/prod_HD_PLANCHA_L.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/prod_HD_PLANCHA_R.png 
 560 
  
 