   
 Stainless steel front, front top ledge, burner box, sides, base and stub back 
 1 1/4" front gas manifold 
 1 1/4" rear gas connection (capped) 
 4" stainless steel stub riser 
 
 
 The performance to tackle today's demands. The flexibility to meet tomorrow's. The V Series is our latest line of intelligently designed heavy duty ranges that features the ultimate in durability, innovative features and true versatility. V Series ranges are modular from top to bottom and side to side, giving you maximum freedom for your kitchen  and your menu. Best of all, the unique design of the V Series allows for complete customization as your needs change. 
 47668356 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/HeavyDutyCookSuites_V-series-lineup-adj.png 
  
  
 573 
  
 