   
 Stainless steel front, front top ledge, burner box, sides, base and stub back 
 1 1/4" diameter front gas manifold 
 3/4" rear gas connection  
 70,000 BTU/hr. input 
 Patented ThreePass heat exchanger providing high efficiency 
 Electronic ignition 
 SoftStart ignition system heats cold oil gently 
 Available with Kleenscreen Plus filtration 
 One year parts and labor warranty 
 
 
 The performance to tackle today's demands. The flexibility to meet tomorrow's. The V Series is our latest line of intelligently designed heavy duty ranges that features the ultimate in durability, innovative features and true versatility. V Series ranges are modular from top to bottom and side to side, giving you maximum freedom for your kitchen  and your menu. Best of all, the unique design of the V Series allows for complete customization as your needs change. 
 47668356 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VIR_1_SF_SIDE_1590_4C.png 
  
  
 574 
  
 