   
 6" stainless steel legs 
 Stainless steel cabinet base doors and adjustable universal slides with stainless steel shelf for cabinet base models (no shelf or slides in 12" wide cabinet bases) 
 Porcelain over steel oven cavity 
 
 
 The performance to tackle today's demands. The flexibility to meet tomorrow's. The V Series is our latest line of intelligently designed heavy duty ranges that features the ultimate in durability, innovative features and true versatility. V Series ranges are modular from top to bottom and side to side, giving you maximum freedom for your kitchen  and your menu. Best of all, the unique design of the V Series allows for complete customization as your needs change. 
 47668356 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/HeavyDutyCookSuites_V-series-lineup-adj.png 
  
  
 575 
  
 