   
 Stainless steel exterior, frame and flanged feet 
 Stainless steel pan with embossed gallon markings and pouring lip strainer 
 Watertight controls and enclosure 
 Electronic ignition (gas models) 
 Stainless steel hinged cover with drip edge 
 Stainless steel drop-down food receiving pan support 
 Solid state temperature controls adjust from 50-425º F 
 "L" faucet bracket adds 3" to width, field installed left or right side 
 
 
 Vulcan's popular V Series braising pans offer more standard features than the competition, including stainless steel  fully-welded one-piece design with coved corners and satin finish (interior and exterior). 
 47668359 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/BraisingPans_VE-G30-right.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VE-G30-left-v1_2.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VE-G30-left-v2_3.png 
 505 
 1 
 