   
 Stainless steel exterior, legs and flanged feet 
 Heavy gauge top with formed drain trough 
 Sliding drain pan 
 Embossed gallons and liter markings 
 
 
 With embossed gallon and liter markings, Vulcan’s spec line tables for electric counter kettles and counter braising tables are designed with operators in mind. With an assortment of models and accessories, we’re sure to have just what you’re looking for.   
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Kettle-VKT50-K6DTT2.png 
  
  
 499 
 5 
 