   
 Stainless steel exterior legs and flanged feet 
 Heavy gauge top with formed drain trough 
 Sliding drain pan 
 Kettles plumbed with steam controls 
 Double pantry faucet 
 
 
 Vulcan’s spec line tables for direct steam counter kettles come with stainless steel exteriors, legs and flanged feet. Other features include double pantry faucets, sliding drain pans and heavy gauge tops with formed drain troughs.   
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Kettle-VKT50-K6DTT2.png 
  
  
 500 
 6 
 