   
 NSF© Compliant 
 All faucets and fillers comply with the new Lead Reduction Legislation in California (AB1953), Vermont and other jurisdictions that have adopted this legislation 
 
 
    Vulcan
makes it simple to find the perfect faucet for your equipment purchase. We
feature a range of common faucets for kettles and braising pans, all of which
are NSF compliant.   
    
    
 
  
  
  
  
 502 
 8 
 