   
 DLX models part of PowerSteam™ Series 
 Super-heated 235º F high energy steam 
 Staged water fill for superior heat up and steam quality 
 Deluxe controls with 60-minute timer, buzzer, and constant steam feature, cook/ready light and power switch 
 Stainless steel exterior and cooking compartments with coved interior corners 
 Heavy duty door and latch mechanism 
 Long-life door gasket with exclusive Vulcan pan guard 
 Split water line connection 
 External deliming port 
 High output stainless steel generator with auto SmartDrain PowerFlush™ System 
 
 
 Vulcan’s Electric Counter Convection Steamers include high-output stainless steel steam generators with manual SmartDrain PowerFlush™ Systems. A selection of options and accessories make it easy to find the perfect steamer for your kitchen.   
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Steamers_2-C24EA5-DLX-right.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Steamers_2-C24EA5-DLX-left_2.png 
  
 488 
 2 
 