   
 Controls with 60-minute timer, buzzer, cook/ready light and power switch 
 Stainless steel exterior and cooking compartment with coved interior corners 
 Heavy gauge stainless steel door 
 Convenient deliming port 
 Split water line connection 
 4" legs 
 
 
 Our 5-Pan Gas Convection Steamers feature convenient de-liming ports and coved interior corners for hassle-free cleaning. Stainless steel exteriors, doors and cooking compartments provide the durability needed in any kitchen. 
 47668355 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Steamers_VSX5G-right.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Steamers_VSX5G-left_2.png 
  
 490 
 4 
 