   
 Super-heated 235º F high energy steam 
 Staged water fill for superior heat up and steam quality 
 Deluxe controls with 60-minute timer, buzzer, and constant steam feature, cook/ready light and power switch 
 Stainless steel exterior and cooking compartments with coved interior corners 
 Heavy duty door and latch mechanism 
 Long-life door gasket with exclusive Vulcan pan guard 
 Split water line connection 
 C24GA comes with 115 V cord and plug 
 External deliming port 
 High output stainless steel mineral tolerant generator 
 
 
   With
the Vulcan PowerSteam™, it’s easy to achieve greater production in a smaller
footprint, all while reducing labor costs. Super-heated, 235° steam makes it
the fastest à la carte steamer, bar none.  
 
 47668355 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Steamers_C24E-G-6-right.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Steamers_C24E-G-6-left_2.png 
  
 491 
 5 
 