   
 Deluxe controls with 60-minute timer, buzzer and constant steam feature, cook/ready light and power switch 
 Stainless steel exterior and cooking compartments with coved interior corners 
 Heavy duty door and latch mechanism 
 Long-life door gasket with exclusive Vulcan pan guard 
 Split water line connection 
 C24GA comes with 115 V cord and plug 
 External deliming port  
 High output stainless steel mineral tolerant generator 
 
 
  Vulcan’s A La Carte Steamers include deluxe controls, heavy duty doors and latch mechanisms, and exclusive Vulcan pan guards. Even though the same says basic, they’re anything but. 
 
  
   
   
 
 47668355 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Steamer-C24GA10-QL.png 
  
  
 492 
 6 
 