   
 All stainless steel construction  
 Interior pan supports removable for easy cleaning  
 Mechanical temperature controls  
 3 wire cooking shelves with VRH8 and 6 racks with VRH88  
 Set of (4) 5" casters (field installed)  
 208/240 V dual voltage, 50/60 Hz, 1-Phase  
 6' power cord with plug (2 cords with plugs with VRH88)  
 250º F roast thermostat allows for roasting and rethermalization  
 Gentle air movement browns and caramelizes with reduced shrinkage 
 
   
 
 Vulcan Cook &amp; Hold Ovens use gently recirculated heated air that moves uniformly and consistently around meats, seafood, poultry, vegetables, baked goods and more. Because the ovens operate at a lower temperature than standard or convection ovens, meats come out richly browned and flavorful, seafood is moist and appetizing, and vegetables are colorful and nutritious. 
 48031970 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VRH8_R_5496.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VRH8_F_0008_2.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VRH88_2197.png 
 800 
  
 