   
 All stainless steel construction 
 Interior pan supports removable for easy cleaning 
 Solid state temperature controls 
 2 wire cooking racks with VCH5 and VCH8; 4 racks with VCH16 and VCH88 
 Set of (4) 5" casters 
 208/240 V dual voltage, 50/60 Hz, 1-Phase 
 6' power cord with plug (2 cords with plugs for VCH88) 
 350º F thermostat allows for roasting, baking and rethermalization 
 Digital time and temperature settings with easy-to-use knob; no touch pads 
 Convected air browns and caramelizes with reduced shrinkage 
 Removable self-contained control and heating module top 
 Heavy duty door latch 
 Rugged hinges and silicone gaskets 
 Sturdy 5" casters 
 Thick fibrous insulation—maximum thermal efficiency 
 
 
 Vulcan Cook &amp; Hold Ovens use gently recirculated heated air that moves uniformly and consistently around meats, seafood, poultry, vegetables, baked goods and more. Because the ovens operate at a lower temperature than standard or convection ovens, meats come out richly browned and flavorful, seafood is moist and appetizing, and vegetables are colorful and nutritious. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VCH16_10.png 
  
  
 799 
  
 