   
 Ideal for schools, restaurants and hospitals 
 All stainless steel construction 
 Field reversible doors 
 Removable interior pan supports 
 Accepts 18" x 26" or 12" x 20" pans 
 Blower provides superior heat distribution and recovery 
 (4) 5" casters, 2 swivel with locks and 2 rigid 
 ENERGY STAR® Qualified 
 
 
 Designed to keep foods hot and delicious from cooking to serving. With quality features like energy-efficient cabinet design for quicker preheating and recovery times and rugged tubular steel frames, you'll find our Heated Holding Cabinets a valuable addition to your operation. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/HoldingCabinet_VBP15I_Right.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/HoldingCabinet_VBP15I_Front_2.png 
  
 427 
 1 
 