   
 All stainless steel construction 
 Dutch doors front and back 
 Removable interior pan supports 
 Accepts 18" x 26" or 12" x 20" pans 
 Blower provides superior heat distribution and recovery 
 (4) 5" casters—2 swivel with locks and 2 rigid 
 ENERGY STAR® qualified 
 
 
 Designed to keep foods hot and delicious from cooking to serving. With quality features like energy-efficient cabinet design for quicker preheating and recovery times and rugged tubular steel frames, you'll find our Heated Holding Cabinets a valuable addition to your operation. The integrated frame design provides the strength of a reach-in cabinet with the flexibility of a pass through. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VPT15_51.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VPT15_13_2.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VPT15_08_3.png 
 754 
 2 
 