   
 Stainless steel front, top, sides and rear enclosure panel 
 Stainless steel door with double pane windows 
 4" adjustable chrome legs 
 Porcelain enamel on steel oven interior 
 5 oven racks 
 60-minute timer with audible alarm 
 1-piece cool-to-the-touch door handles 
 
 
 The versatile performance you need for preparing a varied menu with consistently great results. With gentle air circulation and even heat distribution, these all-purpose ovens produce delicious, evenly cooked casseroles, meats, vegetables and baked goods. They also save on operating costs with an energy-efficient heat recovery system. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Ovens_ECO_2D_STAND_CAASTERS_R_4062.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Ovens_ECO_2D_STAND_F_4029_2.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/ECO_2_D_Stand_Front_25181_wSS_Legs_3.png 
 426 
 2 
 