   
 Stainless steel front, top, sides and rear enclosure panel 
 Stainless steel door with double pane windows 
 4" adjustable chrome legs 
 Porcelain enamel on steel oven interior 
 5 oven racks 
 60-minute timer with audible alarm 
 1-piece cool-to-the-touch door handles 
 
 
 Many of the same features that make Vulcan full-size convection ovens such great performers are also available in space-saving GCO/ECO Series half-size ovens. Available in gas or electric, you can select the model that's just right for your cooking, roasting and baking needs. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Ovens_GC02D_Right.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Ovens_GC02D_Front_2.png 
  
 425 
 1 
 