   
 Stainless steel front, sides and top 
 Stainless steel doors with double pane windows 
 1/2 HP 2-speed oven blower motor; 115/60/1 with 6' cord and plug 
 Oven cool switch for rapid cool down 
 Porcelain enamel on steel oven interior 
 5 nickel-plated oven racks with 11 rack positions 
 Interior oven light 
 1-piece cool-to-the-touch door handles 
 44,000 BTU/hr burner per oven section 
 Electronic spark ignition 
 3/4" rear gas connection 
 Internal combination gas pressure regulator and safety solenoid system 
 ENERGY STAR® Qualified 
 
   
 NOTE: Available in single- and double-stacked configurations. 
 
 The versatile performance you need for preparing a varied menu with consistently great results. With gentle air circulation and even heat distribution, these all-purpose ovens produce delicious, evenly cooked casseroles, meats, vegetables and baked goods. They also save on operating costs with an energy-efficient heat recovery system. 
 47962761 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Ovens_VC_44_D_R_4075.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Ovens_VC44_GD_4024_2.png 
  
 421 
 1 
 