   
 Left-side controls available for operations that require flexibility 
 Stainless steel front, sides, top and door gaskets 
 Choice of single- or double-stacked configuration 
 Easy-to-clean porcelain-coated enameled steel interior 
 60,000 BTU/hr total input 
 Gentle bake mode selector switch for greater flexibility 
 Independently operatored doors with full-length hinge pins and welded full door frames 
 Full-view door windows 
 1/2 HP 2-speed fan motor 
 Auxiliary fan switch for rapid cooldown 
 European-style, easy-to-replace interior lights 
 11 position rack guide and 5 nickel-plated oven racks (per section) 
 3/4" gas connection with internal combination gas pressure regulator and safety solenoids system (Interconnecting piping supplied on double deck models for single point gas connection.) 
 
 
 Vulcan's SG Series Convection Ovens have been redesigned to deliver the perfect combination of performance and control. The versatile performance you need for preparing a varied menu with consistently great results. With gentle air circulation and even heat distribution, these all-purpose ovens produce delicious, evenly cooked casseroles, meats, vegetables and baked goods. They also save on operating costs with an energy-efficient heat recovery system. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Ovens_SG44_D_R_4057.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Ovens_SG44_D_4046_2.png 
  
 423 
 3 
 