   
 Stainless steel marine edge top installs securely to the convection oven, capturing condensation and providing a sturdy base for a steamer 
 Kit includes splash shield for the rear of the oven to protect electrical components 
 Use with any Vulcan C24EO steamer (requires optional 4" legs) 
 
 
 The versatile performance you need for preparing a varied menu with consistently great results. With gentle air circulation and even heat distribution, these all-purpose ovens produce delicious, evenly cooked casseroles, meats, vegetables and baked goods. They also save on operating costs with an energy-efficient heat recovery system. 
  
  
  
  
 424 
 4 
 