   
 Patent pending FivePass™ heat transfer system for maximum cooking efficiency and shorter cook time 
 SoftStart™ ignition system heats cold oil gently, extending oil life 
 Significantly lower idle rate saves energy 
 Reliable sealed combustion technology 
 Lower flue temperature reduces kitchen A/C costs 
 Adjustable casters—2 swivel with locks and 2 rigid 
 Sealed combustion system 
 Available with Solid State Analog Knob (A), Solid State Digital (D) or Programmable Computer (C) controls 
 Available with KleenScreen PLUS® Filtration System 
 Stainless steel cabinet and fry tank 
 Electronic ignition standard—1 power button starts the fryer instantly 
 10-year limited tank warranty 
 
 NOTE: KleenScreen PLUS® Filtration System in not recommended for solid shortening. 
 
 The ENERGY STAR® qualified PowerFry™ VK Series Fryer redefines the traditional fryer by using a patent pending FivePass™ heat transfer system for maximum efficiency. The FivePass™ technology utilizes every angle of the tank to heat oil and prevent heat from escaping through the exhaust hood, resulting in higher performance and shorter cook times, saving your operation money and energy. Fully designed and executed with end-users in mind, the PowerFry™ VK Series Fryer is easy to use and clean, which can be a significant burden for high-volume foodservice operations. With quick recovery and uniform heat distribution, precise results are delivered consistently from batch to batch. FCSI named the PowerFry™ VK Series Fryer as one of the "Top 10 Most Innovative Products for 2012," and it also won the Gas Foodservice Equipment Network’s prestigious Blue Flame Product of the Year Award in 2013 for outstanding natural gas technology.  
 48031968 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/PowerFry_2VK45DF_Front_2.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/PowerFry_2VK45DF_Right.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/PowerFry_2VK45DF_Front_Open_3.png 
 382 
 5 
 