   
 Patented ThreePass™ Heat Exchanger 
 Stainless steel cabinet and fry tank 
 Twin baskets 
 1/2" ID and 3/4" OD rear gas connection 
 1/4" rear connection for 2, 3 or 4 battery fryers 
 Adjustable casters—2 swivel with locks and 2 rigid 
 Sealed combustion system 
 Tank brush, clean-out rod and drain extension 
 Available with Solid State Analog Knob (A), Solid State Digital (D) or Programmable Computer (C) controls 
 All TR Series Gas Fryers are standard with electronic ignition—power button starts the fryer instantly 
 Lower flue temperatures 
 10-year limited tank warranty 
 
 
 Featuring a unique ThreePass™ Heat Exchanger, this ENERGY STAR® qualified fryer delivers shorter cook times for optimum throughput, quick temperature recovery, less oil absorption and reduced oil top-off. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/PowerFry_2VK45DF_Front_2.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/PowerFry_2VK45DF_Right.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/PowerFry_2VK45DF_Front_Open_3.png 
 780 
 4 
 