   
 Stainless steel cabinet 
 Stainless steel curved pan to allow for easy removal of food products 
 Adjustable casters—2 locking, 2 non-locking 
 Storage area behind door 
 Grease strip connecting bracket and all hardware included 
 Can be installed on the left, right or both sides of the fryer 
 
   
 
 Convenient Fry Dump Station for both Gas and Electric Fryers. Frymates can be freestanding or an "add-on" to the left, right or both sides of a freestanding fryer or KleenScreen PLUS® System. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/FRYMATE-DX15R_5635.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/FRY-MATE-VX15_F5692_2.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/FRYMATE_Foodwarmer_VX15_Right_3.png 
 581 
 