   
 18 mm (≈ 3/4") Rapid Recovery™ composite griddle plate 
 304 Series stainless steel cooking surface offers exceptional cleanability and reduces flavor transfer between foods 
 True "corner-to-corner" temperature control (+/- 12º F to set point at idle) across cooking surface to maximize production capacity in every size 
 Heavy load cooking efficiency over 40%. Almost 50 lbs/hr production capacity** 
 27 500 BTU/hr atmospheric U-shaped burners for balanced heat distribution 
 Electronic ignition with solid state temperature control of 150-450º F range 
 Low-profile chassis provides working height of 11" on 4" adjustable legs 
 High capacity 6 quart grease drawer 
 Heavy gauge knob guards protect your temperature settings 
 
 
 The Vulcan RRG series offers restaurant operators a heavy duty griddle solution that delivers high efficiency, high production capability and labor savings. The proprietary composite griddle plate has the fastest heat transfer characteristics of any griddle design in its class. The RRG provides the operator with true "corner to corner" temperature uniformity - allowing them to use every square inch for production. Uniform temperature helps the kitchen deliver high quality product. The stainless steel cooking surface is easy to clean and doesn't require the use of caustic cleaners, griddle bricks or special tools. 
 47962760 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/48RRG-2600x1000.png 
  
  
 407 
 2 
 