   
 Fully welded, all stainless steel mounting frame and spring-assist lift arm assembly  
 Thermostat is adjustable and supports cooking temperatures of 200-450º F. 
 Heating elements are thermally protected 
 Illuminated power switch and heating element cycle light 
 5/8" composite construction cooking platen maximizes production in each 12" cooking zone 
 GTS12 units are compatible with new or existing Vulcan Heavy Duty Gas Griddles RRG, 900RX/RE and MSA Series units with 4" backsplashes 
 GTS12 units can be added and field-installed as production requirements increase 
 Available 208 or 240 V, 50/60 Hz, 1-Phase 
 6' power cord standard 
 1-year limited parts and labor warranty standard 
 1 Gap Adjustment accessory (GADJUST-GTS) provided with each GTS12 unit standard 
 
 
 Designed to meet the needs of customers in the foodservice industry, the new Vulcan griddle top is double sided to increase the speed of service and improve ticket times. The "contact clamshell" uses the same unique griddle plates as the Vulcan Rapid Recovery Griddle, which offers the fastest transfer of heat in the industry. The top and bottom heating provides the most efficient method to conduct large batch cooking such as steaks, burgers, or quesadillas. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/RRG36_GTS12_R_D_5918.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/RRG36_GTS12_F_D_5938_2.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/RRG36_GTS12_R_U_5924.png 
 413 
 