   
 Patented grate design virtually eliminates flare-ups 
 Energy-efficient 22,000 BTU/hr independent burner sections every 12" with high range gas controls 
 11" x 25" stainless steel cooking grids providing ≈ 2 sq. ft of cooking area in each burner zone 
 Heavy gauge steel emitter panels produce rapid-cooking infrared energy 
 Rotary piezo provides direct spark ignition to burners 
 Cool bull nose design keeps the front rail cool to the touch at all times 
 Stainless steel sides, control panel, top trim and removable heat shield 
 Full width, stainless steel front crumb tray 
 All units shipped with 4" heavy duty adjustable legs 
 
 
  IRX™ technology delivers increased production capacity, decreased gas usage and increased food quality—experience true infrared cooking and taste the difference. 
 
 Maximized Production 
 Energy Efficiency 
 Ease of Operation 
 Increased Product Yield 
 Virtually No Flare-Ups  
 
 
 47963703 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Charbroiler_VTEC48.png 
  
  
 441 
  
 