   
 Best temperature profile of any charbroiler in its class—more usable heat (600-700º F) into the grate area for maximum production capacity and productivity 
 Powerful 18,000 BTU/hr burner in each 6" broiler section with wide range manual gas valves 
 Vulcan's "supercharger" plates are standard—improving energy utilization and performance across the burner box 
 Fully welded chassis, heavy duty cast iron burners, radiants and grates provide exceptional durability 
 Stainless steel sides, control panel, backsplash, top trim and grease trough for easy clean-up 
 Deflector tray removes for easy cleaning, improves temperature profile and keeps heat away from expensive under-counter refrigeration 
 Easy-to-light design for maximum operator convenience 
 
 
 VACB Charbroilers offer the most uniform deck profile of any heavy duty counter charbroiler in its class. Heavy duty 24" deep cast iron grates, cast iron radiants and cast iron burner deliver years of reliable performance in the most punishing environments. The Achiever's unique "supercharger" construction and heat deflector panels keep the heat focused above each burner, create a "cool zone" below the unit and protect your refrigerated base. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VACB47-2600x1100.png 
  
  
 414 
 