   
 Heavy duty cast iron char-radiants and reversible 5 1/4" wide 
 Flame Arrestor broiling grates are standard 
 14,500 BTU/hr heavy duty cast iron burners in each 6" section 
 Deflector panels below burners focus heat into cooking—design keeps crumb tray cool and protects refrigerated bases 
 Stainless steel sides, control panel, top rim, backsplash and full width grease trough 
 Standing pilot ignition system with infinite control gas valve burner controls 
 13" working height—14 3/4" overall height on 4" adjustable legs 
 3/4" gas connection with pressure regulator 
 1-year parts and labor warranty 
 
 
 The VCCB design is positioned to support the production needs of a busy casual dining restaurant. The 22" deep grates are standard along with 14,500 BTU aluminized steel burners every six inches. Also includes under-burner heat deflectors to protect your refrigerated base. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VCCB47-2600x1000.png 
  
  
 415 
 