   
 1" thick polished steel griddle plate—a full 20 1/2" deep, with 3 1/2" tapered stainless steel splashes 
 Embedded, mechanical snap-action thermostats for high performance and optimal response time. Temperature adjusts from 200-450º F 
 (1) 25,000 BTU/hr U-shaped aluminized steel burner for every 12" of griddle width 
 1 pilot safety valve for every 2 burners; safety will completely shut off gas to pilot and burners if pilot extinguishes 
 Fully welded stainless and aluminized steel chassis frame 
 High capacity 4 1/2 quart grease can 
 12 1/2" cooking height on 4" adjustable legs 
 All units shipped equipped for Natural Gas with conversion kit for LP service 
 
 
 With a class-leading 1" thick, top-seam welded griddle plate, the VCRG-T model griddle delivers increased production capacity, faster recovery and superior temperature control. The VCRG-T design includes an embedded snap-action control thermostat and full supervised pilot and burner safety system. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VCRG24-T-2000x1300.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VCRG24-T1_0006_2.png 
  
 417 
 1 
 