   
 1" thick polished steel griddle plate—a full 20 1/2" deep, with 3 1/2" tapered stainless steel splashes 
 1 infinite heat control valve per burner 
 (1) 25,000 BTU/hr U-shaped aluminized steel burner for every 12" of griddle width 
 Standing pilot ignition system 
 Fully welded stainless and aluminized steel chassis frame 
 High capacity 4 1/2 quart grease can 
 12 1/2"; cooking height on 4" adjustable legs 
 All units shipped for Natural Gas with conversion kit for LP service 
 
 
 With a class-leading 1" thick, top-seam welded griddle plate, this manual griddle contains many of the same high-quality features as the VCRG-T. Made with the most durable materials, stainless and aluminized steel, this product will exceed all your expectations. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VCRG24-M1_0012_2.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VCRG24-M-2000x1300.png 
  
 418 
 2 
 