   
 Heavy duty cast iron char-radiants and reversible 5 1/4" wide Flame Arrestor broiling grates are standard 
 14,500 BTU/hr heavy duty cast iron burners in each 6" section 
 Deflector panels below burners focus heat into cooking—design keeps crumb tray cool and protects refrigerated bases 
 Stainless steel sides, control panel, top rim  backsplash and full width grease trough 
 Protected flash tube ignition system with infinite control gas valve burner controls 
 13" working height on 4" adjustable legs 
 All units shipped for Natural Gas with conversion kit for LP service 
 
 
 This Charbroiler recognizes the production needs of the independent operator. A low profile unit with a full 22" deep cooking grate. Heavy cast iron burners, radiants and grates provide durability and performance in a busy kitchen. Full-width crumb trays and standard under-burner heat deflectors improve cooking performance and help protect under-counter refrigeration. VCRB units are easily convertible from Natural Gas to LP in the field. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VCRB25-2200x1300.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VCRB25-1_6486_2.png 
  
 419 
 3 
 