   
 Cast iron 25,000 BTU/hr 2-piece lift-off burners offer superior heating and flexibility 
 1 infinite heat control valve per burner 
 1 protected standing pilot for every 2 burners reduces gas consumption and protects against spill-over 
 Heavy duty cast iron top grates, 1 per burner, are designed to support heavy pans and stockpots 
 Fully welded stainless and aluminized steel chassis frame 
 All units shipped for Natural Gas with conversion kit for LP service 
 
 
 Made with best in class design, the top of the burner head is removable, so when spills happen, you can keep the unit clean and ready for use. The VCRH Hot Plate design includes a protected flash tube ignition system (1 for every 2 burners) that can save operators hundreds of dollars in fuel costs each year. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/VCRH24-1_6493.png 
  
  
 420 
 4 
 