   
 Stainless steel front, top and sides 
 Infinite adjustment temperature control 
 Six 11,000 BTU/hr bar type burners with stainless steel radiants; 66,000 BTU/hr total input 
 Standing pilot ignition system 
 Chrome plated trigger grip control handle provides positive positioning of the broiling carriage. Heavy duty chrome plated broiling grid measures 27 1/2" w x 13" d 
 Removable full width spillage pan 
 3/4" top gas connection and gas pressure regulator 
 One year limited parts and labor warranty 
 
 
    When
orders stack up, Vulcan’s Heavy Duty Salamander Broilers ensure rapid recovery
times for maximum productivity. Available single- or double-deck with a variety
of bases, they’re an effective addition to any kitchen.   
    
    
 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Salamander.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Salamander_front.png 
  
 790 
  
 