   
 Manual controls with 60-minute timer, buzzer and ready light 
 Stainless steel exterior 
 Stainless steel cooking compartments with coved interior corners 
 Heavy duty door and latch mechanism 
 Long-life door gasket with exclusive Vulcan pan guard 
 Split water line connection 
 External deliming port 
 High output stainless steel generator with manual SmartDrain PowerFlush™ System 
 
 
   Vulcan’s À la Carte Steamersinclude deluxe controls, heavy duty doors and latch mechanisms, and exclusive Vulcan pan guards. Even though the same says basic, they’re anything but. 
 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Steamer-C24EA3-BSC-STAND-28XSGL--QL.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/Steamers_C24EA5-BSC-left.png 
  
 792 
 3 
 