   
 Energy-efficient 24,000 BTU/hr infrared burners for effective heat distribution every 12" 
 1" thick steel plate with embedded solid state temperature control over a 150-550°F range 
 Electronic ignition and pilot protection system 
 Chassis provides working height of 14.5" on 4" adjustable legs 
 Heavy gauge knob guards protect your temperature settings 
 Cool bull nose design keeps the front rail cool to the touch at all times 
 High capacity 6 quart grease drawer - (2) for 60" and 72" sizes 
 
 
 Vulcan Custom Chain Griddles use IRX™ technology to deliver ultimate efficiency and high-volume productivity. Heat is distributed evenly, so it’s easy to cook a great-tasting, consistent product every time. 
 47963703 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/CGG_36_front_1069.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/CGG_36_SIDE_CP_1097.png 
  
 794 
 1 
 