   
  Engineered and assembled with pride in Louisville, Kentucky. 
 Just three knobs, no modes, only temperature, time and humidity. 
 Patent-pending humidity level control automatically adjusts after setting temperature. 
 Exclusive Precision Humidity Control ensures accurate humidity for repeatable results while providing efficiency in energy and water usage. 
 Multiple cooking capabilities from one piece of equipment: baking, steaming, roasting, air-fry, rethermalization, proofing, finishing, poaching, stewing, low temp and defrosting. 
 Boilerless combi which uses direct steam creation for optimized cooking capability and production with minimal energy and water consumption. 
 Auto-reversing fan with electrical braking system on fan motor. 
 Large LED displays for temperature, time and humidity controls. 
 Temperature range: 80-450°F 
 Timer range: continuous (--:--) up to 23:59 hours and minutes 
 Humidity range: 0-100% 
 Visual recall display of actual temperature and humidity LED’s. 
 Timer reloads for batch cooking after completion of timed cycle. 
 Flashing door lights &amp; audible alarm system alert user when cooking cycle finished. 
 Halogen lights (3) built into door behind heat reflective inner glass. 
 Standard with rack guides and (4) unique stainless steel wire racks with cutout design for easy access to pans. 
 Machine diagnostics accessed thru controls or via USB. 
 Cool to the touch &amp; energy efficient heat reflective tempered glass door. 
 All stainless steel interior cooking compartment, top, sides and fully insulated. 
 One year limited parts and labor warranty. 
 
 
 The new Vulcan Combi. Just set temperature and time, it sets the humidity. 
  
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/ABC7G_Front_4Racks_CL.png 
 /uploadedImages/Vulcan/Vulcan_Categories/ABC7G_Front_4Racks_OP.png 
  
 811 
  
 