   
 Stainless steel front, sides and base 
 1 1/4 in. diameter front gas manifold (single deck models only) 
 Infrared broilers have four each 25,000 BTU/hr burners per deck 
 Ceramic radiant broilers have three 32,500 BTU/hr per deck 
 Up to 1000 degree searing temperatures on grid 
 Two infinite heat controls per deck 
 Spring balanced, five-position grid 
 One year parts and labor warranty 
 
 
  
  
  
  
  
 547 
  
 