   ITW FEG earns highest ENERGY STAR award for industry-leading fourth consecutive year  &#160; 
   Troy, Ohio –  The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) has recognized ITW Food Equipment Group─North America (ITW FEG) with a 2013 ENERGY STAR® Partner of the Year─Sustained Excellence Award for its continued leadership in protecting the environment through superior energy efficiency. ITW FEG's accomplishments are to be recognized at an awards ceremony in Washington, D.C., on March 26. An ENERGY STAR Partner since 2008, this is the fourth year that the ITW FEG has received the Sustained Excellence award.&#160; 
 The ITW FEG companies receiving recognition for leadership across the ENERGY STAR program are Hobart, Traulsen, Baxter, Stero, Vulcan, Wittco and Wolf. These companies offer a total of 512 ENERGY STAR qualified units and assist foodservice and grocery operators in their drive to increase energy efficiency through robust customer education and product-focused initiatives. 
 "As a leading foodservice equipment manufacturer and ENERGY STAR partner, we remain committed to helping foodservice and grocery customers design and operate sustainable kitchens that are more efficient, productive and environmentally sound," said Chris O'Herlihy, executive vice president, ITW FEG Worldwide. 
 Top companies and organizations across the United States are leading the way toward a more energy-efficient future through participation in ENERGY STAR. Over the last 20 years, American businesses and families have saved more than $230 billion on utility bills and prevented more than 1.8 billion metric tons of greenhouse gas emissions. 
 "EPA is recognizing ITW Food Equipment Group for earning EPA's highest ENERGY STAR award ─ the 2013 Partner of the Year─Sustained Excellence Award," said Bob Perciasepe, Acting Administrator, U.S. Environmental Protection Agency. "ITW FEG leads the field with their commitment to energy efficiency and demonstrates how all Americans can save energy, save money, and create a healthier environment." 
 The 2013 Partner of the Year─Sustained Excellence Awards are given to a select group of organizations that have exhibited outstanding leadership year after year. These winners have reduced greenhouse gas emissions by setting and achieving aggressive goals, and employing innovative energy-efficiency approaches. These awards recognize ongoing leadership across the ENERGY STAR program, including energy-efficient products, services, new homes and buildings in the commercial, industrial and public sectors. Award winners are selected from the nearly 20,000 organizations that participate in the ENERGY STAR program. 
  About ITW Food Equipment Group–North America  An ENERGY STAR Partner of the Year─Sustained Excellence Award recipient in 2010, 2011, 2012 and 2013 and ENERGY STAR partner since 2008, ITW Food Equipment Group–North America is the parent organization of independent companies such as Hobart ( www.hobartcorp.com ), Traulsen ( www.traulsen.com ), Baxter ( www.baxterbakery.com ), Stero ( www.stero.com ), Vulcan ( www.vulcanequipment.com ), Wittco ( www.wittco.com ) and Wolf ( www.wolfequipment.com ), all of which design and manufacture commercial food equipment for foodservice and grocery customers. 
  About ENERGY STAR  ENERGY STAR was introduced by the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency in 1992 as a voluntary market-based partnership to reduce greenhouse gas emissions through increased energy efficiency. Today, ENERGY STAR offers businesses and consumers energy-efficient solutions to save energy, money and help protect the environment for future generations. Nearly 20,000 organizations are ENERGY STAR partners committed to improving the energy efficiency of products, homes and buildings. For more information about ENERGY STAR, visit www.energystar.gov or call toll-free 1-888-STAR-YES (1-888-782-7937). 