 &#160;  Gas Foodservice Equipment Network Selects The PowerFry™ VK Series Fryer As Product Of The Year  &#160; &#160; &#160; 
  Gas Foodservice Equipment Network &#160;(GFEN) selects Vulcan's PowerFry™ VK Series Fryer to receive the 2013 Blue Flame Award for Product of the Year, highlighting the company's&#160;commitment to producing leading technology that supports the Gas Foodservice Industry.&#160;Recognizing innovative natural gas appliances each year, GFEN's Blue Flame Award emphasizes the importance of introducing new and improved cooking equipment to the marketplace and rewards manufacturers' outstanding efforts in research and development. 
   
 Ranked best by GFEN, the&#160;PowerFry™ Fryer&#160;was evaluated in multiple categories ranging from creativity, technology and quality to productivity, safety and environmental impact.&#160;Its state-of-the-art features include: 
  FivePass™ heat transfer system —transfers heat to the oil more efficiently, resulting in faster recovery and reduced cooking time  &#160; 
  SoftStart™ ignition system —heats cold oil gently, extending oil life 
  Lower flue temperature —decreases kitchen A/C&#160;costs 
  Significantly lower idle rate —reduces gas consumption and saves energy&#160;&#160; 
 "As a leading commercial equipment provider, it's our mission to help foodservice professionals streamline their&#160;operational needs with technologically advanced products," said&#160;Paul Forrest,&#160;General Manager of Vulcan's Fryer Cooking Division. "The PowerFry™ VK Series Fryer exemplifies our efforts to design equipment that seamlessly increases producitivity, reduces energy costs, and delivers exceptional cooking results." 
 Vulcan will be presented with the Blue Flame Award by GFEN’s chairperson and executive leaders at the NAFEM Show in Orlando, FL on February 7, 2013. The PowerFry™ VK Series Fryer was also named&#160;one of the&#160; "Top 10 Most Innovative Products for 2012" by Foodservice Consultant Society International (FCSI). &#160; 