    ITW FEG earns highest ENERGY STAR award for industry-leading third consecutive year    
  Troy, OH  – The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) has awarded ITW Food Equipment Group–North America (ITW FEG) a 2012 ENERGY STAR Sustained Excellence Award in recognition of its continued leadership in protecting the environment through energy efficiency. A leading manufacturer of commercial food equipment, ITW FEG's accomplishments will be recognized at an awards ceremony in Washington, D.C. on March 15, 2012, which marks the 20 th  anniversary of ENERGY STAR. 
 ITW FEG, an ENERGY STAR partner since 2008, will be honored for its long-term leadership and continued efforts in helping to make foodservice and grocery operations more energy efficient, sustainable and profitable. Hobart, Traulsen, Stero, Vulcan, Wittco and Wolf are among the ITW FEG companies that support foodservice and grocery customers in their efforts to reduce costs, consume less water and electricity, and decrease waste.  Across the United States, top companies and organizations are leading the way toward a more energy-efficient future through participation in ENERGY STAR. 
 Over the past 20 years, American businesses and families have saved nearly $230 billion on utility bills and prevented greenhouse gas emissions equal to those from more than 350 million vehicles with help from ENERGY STAR. 
 “Our sustainability commitment remains strong—to design and manufacture commercial food equipment that allows foodservice and grocery operations to increase energy efficiency and reduce environmental impact," said Chris O'Herlihy, Executive Vice President, ITW FEG Worldwide. "Through our strategic partnership with ENERGY STAR, as well as customer education and product-focused initiatives, ITW FEG companies will continue to lead sustainability efforts across the commercial foodservice industry." 
 The 2012 Sustained Excellence Awards are given to a select group of organizations that have exhibited outstanding leadership year after year. These winners have reduced greenhouse gas emissions by setting and achieving aggressive goals, employing innovative approaches and showing others what can be accomplished through energy efficiency. These awards recognize ongoing leadership across the ENERGY STAR program including energy-efficient products, services and new homes and buildings in the commercial, industrial and public sectors. Award winners are selected from about 20,000 organizations that participate in the ENERGY STAR program. 
 "As we celebrate the 20 th  anniversary of the ENERGY STAR program, EPA is proud to recognize ITW FEG with the 2012 ENERGY STAR Sustained Excellence Award," said EPA Administrator Lisa P. Jackson. "ITW FEG and all our ENERGY STAR award winners are helping Americans find cost-effective ways to save energy in everything we do, which is good for our climate, our health, and our future." 
  About ITW Food Equipment Group–North America   
 An ENERGY STAR Sustained Excellence award recipient in 2010, 2011 and 2012 and an ENERGY STAR partner since 2008, ITW Food Equipment Group–North America is the parent organization of independent companies such as Hobart ( www.hobartcorp.com ), Traulsen ( www.traulsen.com ), Stero ( www.stero.com ), Vulcan ( www.vulcanequipment.com ), Wittco ( www.wittco.com ) and Wolf ( www.wolfequipment.com ), all of which design and manufacture commercial food equipment for foodservice and grocery customers. 
  About ENERGY STAR   
 ENERGY STAR was introduced by the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency in 1992 as a voluntary market-based partnership to reduce greenhouse gas emissions through increased energy efficiency. Now celebrating its 20 th  anniversary, ENERGY STAR offers businesses and consumers energy-efficient solutions to save energy, money and help protect the environment for future generations. About 20,000 organizations are ENERGY STAR partners committed to improving the energy efficiency of products, homes, buildings and businesses. For more information about ENERGY STAR, visit  www.energystar.gov  or call toll-free 1-888-STAR-YES (1-888-782-7937). 
  FOR FURTHER INFORMATION:   
 ITW – Lisa McLaughlin, (513) 346-3487,  lisa.mclaughlin@gyro.com  EPA – Courtney Upshall, (202) 343-9948,  Upshall.courtney@epa.gov  Vulcan &amp; Wolf – Susan Gunther, (410) 715-1500,  susang@marriner.com   