    Deal Also Includes Rights to Sell Award-Winning TEC Searmaster Charbroiler Line    
 Illinois Tool Works Food Equipment Group North America announces the acquisition of several assets from the commercial business of TEC (Thermal Engineering Corporation) for use within the Vulcan line of cooking equipment. As part of the acquisition, Vulcan will own the exclusive rights to TEC’s patented infrared cooking technology in the commercial cooking industry and a license to sell TEC’s Searmaster Charbroiler product line. TEC, founded in 1961 and based in Columbia, SC, will continue operations and will focus on their other lines of business which include residential bar-b-ques and industrial paint drying systems as well as research and development. 
 The infrared technology was developed by Bill Best, the founder of TEC, who has more than 100 active and pending patents and is viewed as an expert in thermodynamics. The Searmaster and the infrared cooking technology received the 2006 Kitchen Innovations Award from the National Restaurant Association and the 2006 Blue Flame Award for the most innovative technology from the Gas Foodservice Equipment Network. 
 For chefs and foodservice operators, the benefits of this infrared technology include: 
 
 50% more energy efficient over other burners used in the industry, helping achieve more cost savings and ROI quickly 
 Precise cooking to maximize food quality with higher moisture retention, more consistency and less waste 
 
 The Searmaster has also proven to be easy to maintain, cook on and clean to maximize back-of-house labor. With its stainless steel construction, the product is durable and reliable. 
 Tim Murray, VP/GM of Vulcan FEG Cooking, “When we talk about Vulcan being a leading innovator in the commercial equipment industry, it’s not just lip service. This acquisition is a positive business move because it demonstrates our commitment to delivering the absolute best cooking equipment for our customers.” 