    VHFA18 Set Apart by Efficient Design and Durability for Maximum Performance    
 Leading commercial kitchen equipment provider Vulcan continues to experience strong success with its ENERGY STAR® qualified Non-Insulated Holding Cabinet. With a durable stainless steel design and user-friendly features perfected for foodservice needs, the Vulcan VHFA18 offers superior heating, energy efficiency and operational productivity.   Designed to keep foods hot and delicious from cooking to serving, this energy-saving cabinet has an even heat distribution to secure food temperatures. The VHFA18 also preheats quickly because of the stainless steel construction, an advantage over competing aluminum cabinets.  Features and benefits of the VHFA18 Non-Insulated Holding Cabinet include: 
 
  Energy Efficient  – Cabinet design creates a fast transfer of heat for quicker preheating and recovery times while reducing energy costs 
  Heavy Duty Construction  – Durable polished stainless steel with full size glass door and set of 5” casters: two locking swivel and two rigid 
  Easy-to-Operate  – Top-mounted, recessed control panel includes adjustable dial thermostat, “on”/”off” switch for the fan, and “on” indicator lights for the power and heater 
 
 “Our VHFA18 Non-Insulated Holding Cabinet is a perfect example of how Vulcan is committed to continually developing innovative and relevant equipment. All features are designed to directly benefit operators by delivering precision performance, while still making it easy for any kitchen staff to use,” said Jim Sherman, Sales &amp; Marketing Manager for Holding &amp; Transport, Vulcan. “Vulcan’s dedication to drive consistent results, improve cooking quality and create energy efficiencies has been recognized as best overall in the industry year after year.” 