    Vulcan Steamer Products Earn Overall Award for the First Time    
 Leading commercial kitchen equipment manufacturers Vulcan and Wolf continued the tradition of earning industry recognition by winning ten 2010 Best in Class Awards from  Foodservice Equipment &amp; Supplies . Every year the magazine polls its subscribing foodservice operators, consultants and dealers about products spanning 48 different categories. They are asked to evaluate manufacturers on seven performance factors: product quality, value, design &amp; aesthetics, inventory &amp; availability and information availability as well as service &amp; support and sales representation. 
 For 2010, Vulcan &amp; Wolf received the following FE&amp;S awards: 
    Overall Best in Class    
 
 Steamers – Vulcan 
 Ranges, Gas or Electric – Vulcan 
 Charbroilers – Wolf 
 
   Operators' Best in Class    
 
 Charbroilers – Vulcan 
 Ranges, Gas or Electric – Vulcan 
 Steam Jacketed Kettles – Vulcan 
 Steamers – Vulcan 
 Countertop Griddles – Vulcan 
 
   Dealers' Best in Class    
 
 Charbroilers – Wolf 
 Ranges, Gas or Electric – Wolf 
 
 
  FE&amp;S  noted, "Every foodservice equipment manufacturer has a product or service it believes is superior to the competition. But the only way for those products to truly be considered 'best in class' is to provide value in multiple ways as defined by the customer. These comprehensive results shine a bright light on those that establish the benchmark for understanding and meeting the needs of the entire distribution channel." 
 Tim Murray, President of Vulcan &amp; Wolf, adds "It's a real honor to be recognized again by our valued customers and dealer representatives. Year after year we remain 100% committed to developing 'best in class’ products that deliver the performance foodservice operations demand out of their equipment." 