 &#160;  With Unique Griddle Plate, Product Offers Fastest Transfer of Heat in Industry  &#160; 
 Leading commercial kitchen equipment provider Vulcan announced today the launch of its GTS12 Clamshell Griddle for heavy duty griddles. Designed to meet the needs of customers in the foodservice industry, the new Vulcan griddle top is double sided to increase the speed of service and improve ticket times. 
 The "contact clamshell" uses the same unique griddle plates as the Vulcan Rapid Recovery Griddle, which offers the fastest transfer of heat in the industry. The top and bottom heating provides the most efficient method to conduct large batch cooking such as steaks, burgers, or quesadillas. Vulcan's GTS12 also differentiates itself with being easy to operate manually and without any computer controls.&#160; 
  
 
 
  &#160; 
  Features and benefits of the new Clamshell Griddle also include:  
  Uniglaze Technology&#160; – a non-stick, durable&#160; surface that may eliminate Teflon release sheets; also easy to clean and maintain 
  Embedded Snap-Action Style Thermostat &#160;– provides temperature control (200° to 450°F) needed for increased consistency of cooking 
  Sheathed Mica-Strip &#160;– high efficiency heating elements support high volume production while saving energy 
 





&#160; 
 
 
 
 Additional aspects of Vulcan's GTS12: 
 
 Available as a stand-alone device, mounted on new Vulcan heavy duty griddles or field retro-fitted on existing Vulcan griddles 
 Stainless steel lift arm with spring-assist design ensures durability and easy maintenance 
 Electric griddle models contain a gimbled mechanism that allows the plates to find equilibrium on the griddle for more consistent results while cooking 
 
 Tim Murray, President of Vulcan, notes, "Vulcan is committed to providing high-quality kitchen equipment that is reliable, durable, and energy-efficient. The Clamshell Griddle is a key example of this dedication to creating the most innovative and user friendly products on the market. We heard our griddle customers loud and clear – keep it simple, keep it safe, and deliver the speed and performance I need." 