    Elevated distinction marks third consecutive year ITW FEG is recognized by ENERGY STAR    
  Troy, Ohio  – The U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) today announced that ITW Food Equipment Group–North America (ITW FEG) has been honored with a 2010 ENERGY STAR Sustained Excellence award. ITW FEG's accomplishments are to be recognized at an awards ceremony in Washington, D.C., on March 18. ITW FEG is the only commercial foodservice equipment manufacturer receiving the 2010 Sustained Excellence award. 
 ITW FEG, an ENERGY STAR partner since 2008, will be recognized for the third consecutive year for its long-term commitment to energy efficiency. With 455 ENERGY STAR qualified units, Hobart, Traulsen, Stero, Vulcan, Wittco and Wolf are among the ITW FEG independent companies that support the sustainable initiatives of customers and end-users with new products and technologies that directly address their concerns about operations and the environment. ITW FEG is committed to supporting customers in their drive to cut costs, consume less water and electricity, and decrease waste. Hobart's sustainable design website,  www.hobartcorp.com/sustainabledesign , continues to provide resources on sustainable design efforts and innovation for foodservice and food retail operations. Across the United States, top companies and organizations are leading the way toward a more energy-efficient future through participation in ENERGY STAR. 
 "This award exemplifies how leveraging our strong and ongoing partnership with ENERGY STAR helps us successfully assist foodservice and food retail customers in designing and operating sustainable kitchens that are more efficient, productive and environmentally sound," said John McDonough, president of ITW FEG. "Our years of partnership with ENERGY STAR underscore the value of providing equipment that is engineered for energy efficiency and low water consumption and that is good for our customers and their business—from schools and colleges to hotels and restaurants to hospitals and correctional facilities to grocery stores." 
 Facilities with commercial kitchens are estimated to use five times more energy per square foot than the rest of the building combined. ENERGY STAR estimates that qualified products can save up to as much as 50 percent over their conventional counterparts on electric, gas, water and sewer bills. The Food Service Technology Center estimates that more than half of the commercial foodservice's $10 billion annual energy bill is wasted due to inefficient appliances, refrigeration, hot-water heating, lighting, and heating, ventilation and air conditioning systems. 
 Commercial foodservice equipment that can currently earn the ENERGY STAR include commercial fryers, commercial griddles, commercial hot-food holding cabinets, commercial solid-door refrigerators and freezers, commercial steam cookers, commercial dishwashers, commercial ovens and commercial ice-makers. Energy-efficient equipment in a product category that does not presently have an ENERGY STAR standard can also be included in the kitchen to save energy and water and reduce waste. 
  March 2010   
 ITW Food Equipment Group-North America Receives 2010 ENERGY STAR ®  Sustained Excellence Award. 
 The 2010 Sustained Excellence Awards are given to a select group of organizations that have consistently exhibited leadership across the ENERGY STAR program. These winners have reduced greenhouse gas emissions by setting and achieving aggressive goals, employing innovative approaches and showing others what can be achieved through energy efficiency. These awards recognize ongoing leadership across the ENERGY STAR program including energy-efficient products, services, new homes and buildings in the commercial, industrial and public sectors. Award winners are selected from more than 17,000 organizations that participate in the ENERGY STAR program. 
 "EPA is pleased to recognize ITW FEG with our highest ENERGY STAR award – the Sustained Excellence Award," said Gina McCarthy, EPA assistant administrator for Air and Radiation. "ITW FEG’s continued leadership and commitment to energy efficiency is a testament to what we can accomplish to reduce greenhouse gas emissions and protect our global environment." 
  About ITW Food Equipment Group–North America A 2010 ENERGY STAR Sustained Excellence award recipient and an ENERGY STAR Partner since 2008, ITW Food Equipment Group–North America (ITW FEG–NA) is the parent organization of independent companies such as  Hobart ,  Traulsen ,  Stero ,  Vulcan ,  Wittco  and  Wolf , all of which design and manufacture commercial food equipment for foodservice and food retail customers. 
  About ENERGY STAR ENERGY STAR was introduced by the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency in 1992 as a voluntary market-based partnership to reduce greenhouse gas emissions through increased energy efficiency. Today, ENERGY STAR offers businesses and consumers energy-efficient solutions to save energy, money and help protect the environment for future generations. More than 17,000 organizations are ENERGY STAR partners committed to improving the energy efficiency of products, homes, buildings and businesses. For more information about ENERGY STAR, visit  www.energystar.gov  or call toll-free 1-888-STAR-YES (1-888-782-7937). 
  FOR FURTHER INFORMATION:   
 Tammy Monroe, (513) 346-3436  tammy.monroe@gyrohsr.com   
 Maria Vargas, (202) 343-9178  vargas.maria@epa.gov   