   Vulcan continued its tradition of earning industry recognition for its leading commercial cooking equipment by winning ten 2009 Best in Class awards from  Foodservice Equipment &amp; Supplies  . Every year the magazine polls its subscribing foodservice operators, consultants and dealers about products spanning 44 different categories. They are asked to rate the products on attributes such as quality, value, design &amp; aesthetics, inventory &amp; availability and information availability as well as service &amp; support and sales representation. &#160; 
 For 2009, Vulcan received the following&#160; FE&amp;S &#160;awards:  &#160; 
  Overall Best in Class &#160; 
 •&#160;Charbroilers •&#160;Ranges 
  Operators' Best in Class &#160; 
   •&#160;Charbroilers •&#160;Freestanding Floor Fryers •&#160;Ranges •&#160;Steamers 
  Dealers' Best in Class &#160; 
   •&#160;Charbroilers •&#160;Convection Ovens •&#160;Cooking Suites •&#160;Ranges 
  FE&amp;S &#160;noted that "Every business wants to be considered best in class by its customers, and the manufacturers in the foodservice industry are no exception. By performing at the highest possible levels, the chosen few established a track record for supporting all their customers from specifying consultant to dealer to operator and all points in between." 
 Tim Murray, President of Vulcan, adds "It's an honor to be recognized again as best in class by our valued customers. Vulcan remains committed to developing products that address ever-changing market demands and meet the foodservice industry’s needs. Our top priority is ensuring everything we make consistently delivers the features and performance to deliver the most value and achieve success for our customers."&#160; 