    Several of Vulcan’s Ovens, Cabinets, Steamers, Fryers &amp; Griddles Meet or Exceed Environmental Standards, Helping Operators Save Energy and Improve Bottom Line    
 Vulcan, among the world's largest manufacturers of commercial cooking equipment, was once again recognized by the industry for its energy efficient leadership both on a corporate and product level. 
 As a division of ITW Food Equipment Group-North America (ITW FEG-NA), Vulcan shares in the 2009 ENERGY STAR® Partner of the Year – Product Manufacturer award. This is the second consecutive year the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency (EPA) and the Department of Energy (DOE) has chosen ITW FEG-NA for this honor. With 381 ENERGY STAR qualified units and a 56 percent increase in its ENERGY STAR product offerings over last year, ITW FEG-NA is the only commercial foodservice equipment manufacturer to receive the 2009 ENERGY STAR Partner of the Year award. 
 Vulcan is known for manufacturing innovative products with precision performance and masterful design. Several of these products earned the ENERGY STAR rating, the government-backed national symbol of energy efficiency, including: 
 
 Pressureless Counter Convection Steamers 
 Electric Fryers 
 Holding &amp; Transport Carts and Cabinets, including the Non-Insulated H&amp;T Cabinet which uses 33% less energy to heat and reaches holding temperature 16% faster than competitive products 
 Gas Convection Ovens, including the VC4 Series rated at 46% energy efficiency and the SG4 Series which features an energy-saving, patented “power level” control; the Vulcan products were among the few commercial oven products to receive the energy rating 
 Heavy Duty Gas Griddles, including the new Rapid Recovery Series which are rated as the most efficient griddles in their class by the PG&amp;E Food Service Technology Center 
 
 “Vulcan’s ongoing commitment to energy efficiency is essential to supporting customers in their drive to cut costs, consume less water and electricity, and decrease waste,” said Tim Murray, President of Vulcan. “Developing new products and technologies that directly address concerns about running profitable kitchen operations as well as sustaining the environment will continue to be a top priority in our business planning.” 
 Facilities with commercial kitchens are estimated to use five times more energy per square foot than the rest of the building combined. ENERGY STAR estimates that qualified products can save up to as much as 50 percent over their conventional counterparts on electric, gas, water and sewer bills. 
 The 2009 Partner of the Year awards are given to manufacturers and retailers that successfully promote and deliver ENERGY STAR qualified products, saving consumers and businesses money while reducing greenhouse gas emissions. Award winners are selected from more than 12,000 organizations that participate in the ENERGY STAR program. Currently, commercial foodservice products in six categories can earn the ENERGY STAR rating, including fryers, hot-food holding cabinets, commercial solid-door refrigerators and freezers, and commercial steam cookers, commercial dishwashers and commercial ice-makers. 
  About Vulcan and ITW FEG-NA   
 For over 130 years, Vulcan has been recognized by chefs and operators throughout the world for top-quality, energy-efficient commercial cooking equipment that consistently produces spectacular results. Trust Vulcan to help make culinary creations turn out just right – each and every time. 
 An ENERGY STAR Partner of the Year for two consecutive years, ITW Food Equipment Group–North America (ITW FEG–NA) includes companies such as Vulcan, Hobart ( www.hobartcorp.com ), Stero ( www.stero.com ) and Traulsen ( www.traulsen.com ), all of which design and manufacture commercial food equipment for foodservice and food retail customers. 
  About ENERGY STAR   
 ENERGY STAR was introduced by the U.S. Environmental Protection Agency in 1992 as a voluntary market-based partnership to reduce greenhouse gas emissions through increased energy efficiency. Today, in partnership with the U.S. Department of Energy, ENERGY STAR offers businesses and consumers energy-efficient solutions to save energy, money and help protect the environment for future generations. More than 12,000 organizations are ENERGY STAR partners committed to improving the energy efficiency of products, homes, buildings and businesses. For more information about ENERGY STAR, visit  www.energystar.gov  or call toll-free 1-888-STAR-YES (1-888-782-7937). 